

PERSONAL DATA

- NAME SZYMON MOZOL
- ADDRESS NYSA, MARIACKA 1B/3
- **PHONE NUMBER** +48 512 743 315
- EMAIL
 SZYMONMOZOL123@GMAIL.COM
- in LINKEDIN

WEBSITES

- GITHUB
- ITCH.IO
- NEWGROUNDS
- fi FIVERR
- YOUTUBE

SKILLS

- C#
- UNITY ENGINE
- GIT
- CODE OPTIMIZATION
- DESIGN PRINCIPLES
- DESIGN PATTERNS
- ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES

LANGUAGES

POLISH (NATIVE) ENGLISH (B2) GERMAN (A1)

SZYMON MOZOL

UNITY DEVELOPER/PROGRAMMER

I am a bachelor's degree holder in Computer Science at WSB Merito University in Wrocław with specialization in cloud application developer. I spend most of my time creating games in Unity Engine with emphasis on programming them. I am learning to program in C# but i also know Java and C++. I can write clean, optimal and efficient code. I know the Unity engine very well, I can use event system, animations, UI, particle system, lighting system, sound system, the new Input system, import assets and configure them, handle 2D/3D graphics and much more. Ever since my childhood, I have cultivated a deep fascination for video games. Creating, playing, immersing myself in discussions about them, and avidly watching gaming content are my primary passions.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer Mar 2023 - currently Weni Solutions, Nysa IT specialist - Intern Jan 2023 - Apr 2023 Collins Aerospace, Wrocław **Customer assistant** Jan 2022 - Apr 2022 Zara Poland, Wrocław IT specialist Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 Żabka Poland IT specialist Jan 2019 - Jun 2019 Specialist Hospital MSWiA in Głuchołazy



EDUCATION

2020 - 2023

Bachelor degree WSB Merito University, Wrocław

Secondary education Zespół Szkół i Placówek Oświatowych, Technikum nr 2, Nysa

I also obtained an IT Technician license



CERTIFICATE

•

2023 ISTQB Certified

Tester Foundation Level

2018

Cisco IT Essentials



PRIVACY STATEMENT

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).